

PROFILE

Professional Chef with 22 years of extensive experience in Multi Cuisine. Capable of managing dining services of up to 100 to 350 tables while supervising and motivating staff to perform to best of their abilities across every service. I amlooking forward to a challenging and mutually beneficial relationship that can enhance my knowledge and personality. My work would not be limited to the assigned job, but I wouldalso see to it that I make a significant contribution towards the organization's success and my career as well.

CONTACT

PHONE: 00971 561681985

WEBSITE: Unitedfooides.com

EMAIL:

chefdanishsayyed@outlook.com
chefdanishsayyed@gmail.com

HOBBIES

cooking reading traveling food photo graphing

DANISH AHMED SAYED

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA IN HOTAL MANAGEMENT & CATERING TECHNOLOGY FROM INDIAN TRAINING INSTITUTE

(ITI) MARGOA-GOA PASSED THE FINAL EXAMINATION IN FIRST CLASS ON THE 28TH JUNE 2003 DURATION OF THE COURSE TWO YEARS (JULY- 2001 TO JUNE 2003)

HSC: MAHARASTRA STATE BOARD,2000,53%SSC; MAHARASTRA STATE BOARD, 1998,49% COMPUTERS.

- MICROSOFT WORD
- MICROSOFT EXCEL
- MICROSOFT POWER POINT 2007
- INTERNET

CERTIFICATE IN HEALTH, SAFETY AND ENVIRONMENT QUALITY IN COMPASS GROUP, 15TH ASIAN GAMES, DOHA QATAR. 2006

WORK EXPERIENCE

- HEAD CHEF- AL-Hasna Café, Sharjah, UAE, since July 2022 till present
- CHEF DE CUISINE INNOVATIVE CONCEPT COMPANY LTD (PONGO RESTAURANT) FROM 25 MAY 2021 TIII JUNE 30 2022
- KITCHEN MANAGER, The cheesecake factory, Jeddah (K.S.A), since 1st of June 2013 to 9th May 2021
- Head Chef, Bena Misa, Fine Dine Restaurant, Condolim goa since 15TH September 2012 TO 1st of May 2013.
- Sous Chef, Marcus Bar and Restaurant, Porvorim since Goa, 05TH June 2011 TO 10th August 2012.
- Chef de partie in cold kitchen, Vivanta by taj, Punji Goa, since 04TH May 2009 TO 30th May 2011.
- Commi Beacon Court Hotal, Condolim goa since 16TH October 2008 to 30TH April 2009.
- Commi, Spicy Bella Restaurant, Compal Punji Goa, since 05TH February 2008 TO 15TH September 2008.
- Commi , White Negro Bar and Restaurant, Condolim goa, since 25TH December 2006 TO 05TH January 2008.
- Salad chef Compass Group Short Team Period 2 ½ Month in 15TH ASIAN GAMES DOHA 2006.
- Commi Deva Aya Spa Resort, DIVAR GOA, since 01ST November 2005 TO 03RD September 2006.
- Commi Al Baraha Catering Service, KUWAT since 20TH October 2004 TO 10TH October 2005.
- Commi chef, Annabelle's Catering Service, PATTO PANJIM GOA, SINCE 02ND February 2004 TO 05TH September.

SAMPLE WORKS























